{
  "puzzles" : [
    {
      "id" : "",
      "type" : "trivia",
      "question" : "When is Christmas?",
      "choice" : {
       "a" : "Feb 11",
       "b" : "Mar 25",
       "c" : "Nov 13",
       "d" : "Dec 25"
     },
     "solution" : "d"
   },
   {
      "id" : "",
      "type" : "trivia",
      "question" : "Which is the furthest planet from our Sun?",
      "choice" : {
       "a" : "Ceres",
       "b" : "Pluto",
       "c" : "Uranus",
       "d" : "Neptune"
     },
     "solution" : "d"
   },
   {
      "id" : "",
      "type" : "trivia",
      "question" : "When is Leap Day?",
      "choice" : {
       "a" : "Feb 27",
       "b" : "Feb 28",
       "c" : "Feb 29",
       "d" : "Feb 30"
     },
     "solution" : "c"
   },
   {
      "id" : "",
      "type" : "trivia",
      "question" : "Which country has the most area?",
      "choice" : {
       "a" : "Canada",
       "b" : "Australia",
       "c" : "China",
       "d" : "Brazil"
     },
     "solution" : "a"
   },
   {
    "id" : "",
    "type" : "trivia",
    "question" : "Who is the first president?",
    "choice" : {
     "a" : "George Washington",
     "b" : "Andrew Jackson",
     "c" : "John Quincy Adams",
     "d" : "Thomas Jefferson"
   },
   "solution" : "a"
 },
 {
    "id" : "",
    "type" : "trivia",
    "question" : "Who was the second president assasinated?",
    "choice" : {
     "a" : "Theodore Roosevelt",
     "b" : "John F. Kennedy",
     "c" : "William McKinley",
     "d" : "James A. Garfield"
   },
   "solution" : "a"
 },
 {
  "id" : "",
  "type" : "trivia",
  "question" : "Which of the four has the largest population?",
  "choice" : {
   "a" : "France",
   "b" : "Germany",
   "c" : "Indonesia",
   "d" : "Russia"
 },
 "solution" : "c"
},
{
  "id" : "",
  "type" : "trivia",
  "question" : "Which color has the shortest wavelength?",
  "choice" : {
   "a" : "Cyan",
   "b" : "Blue",
   "c" : "Yellow",
   "d" : "Green"
 },
 "solution" : "b"
},
{
  "id" : "",
  "type" : "trivia",
  "question" : "Which color has the lowest frequency?",
  "choice" : {
   "a" : "Cyan",
   "b" : "Blue",
   "c" : "Yellow",
   "d" : "Green"
 },
 "solution" : "c"
},
{
  "id" : "",
  "type" : "trivia",
  "question" : "Which of these is a secondary color?",
  "choice" : {
   "a" : "Red",
   "b" : "Blue",
   "c" : "Yellow",
   "d" : "Green"
 },
 "solution" : "c"
},
{
  "id" : "",
  "type" : "trivia",
  "question" : "Which DC hero is based out of Central City?",
  "choice" : {
   "a" : "Cyborg",
   "b" : "Superman",
   "c" : "Green Lantern",
   "d" : "Flash"
 },
 "solution" : "d"
},
{
  "id" : "",
  "type" : "trivia",
  "question" : "What is the air speed velocity of an unladen swallow?",
  "choice" : {
   "a" : "African or European?",
   "b" : "11 m/s",
   "c" : "Blue",
   "d" : "I don't know"
 },
 "solution" : "a"
},
{
  "id" : "",
  "type" : "trivia",
  "question" : "What is the air speed velocity of an unladen EUROPEAN swallow?",
  "choice" : {
   "a" : "African or European?",
   "b" : "11 m/s",
   "c" : "Blue",
   "d" : "I don't know"
 },
 "solution" : "b"
},
{
  "id" : "",
  "type" : "trivia",
  "question" : "?",
  "choice" : {
   "a" : "African or European?",
   "b" : "11 m/s",
   "c" : "Blue",
   "d" : "I don't know"
 },
 "solution" : "b"
},
{
  "id" : "",
  "type" : "math",
  "question" : "13 * 17",
  "choice" : {
   "a" : "271",
   "b" : "131",
   "c" : "151",
   "d" : "221"
 },
 "solution" : "d"
},

{
  "id" : "",
  "type" : "math",
  "question" : "9 * 14",
  "choice" : {
   "a" : "156",
   "b" : "116",
   "c" : "126",
   "d" : "236"
 },
 "solution" : "c"
},

{
  "id" : "",
  "type" : "math",
  "question" : "8 * 23",
  "choice" : {
   "a" : "184",
   "b" : "214",
   "c" : "124",
   "d" : "174"
 },
 "solution" : "a"
},

{
  "id" : "",
  "type" : "math",
  "question" : "7 * 26",
  "choice" : {
   "a" : "252",
   "b" : "182",
   "c" : "122",
   "d" : "132"
 },
 "solution" : "b"
}




]
}